{
    "subject": "resource/G\u00e9rard_Debreu",
    "predicate": "ontology/influenced",
    "object": "resource/Jacques_Dr\u00e8ze",
    "human_readable": "G\u00e9rard Debreu was influenced by Jacques Dr\u00e8ze.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9800298810005188,
            "question": "Are there any prominent works by G\u00e9rard Debreu that were influenced by Jacques Dr\u00e8ze?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9760404825210571,
            "question": "Did Jacques Dr\u00e8ze have a significant impact on G\u00e9rard Debreu's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9515493512153625,
            "question": "Who influenced G\u00e9rard Debreu?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9279388189315796,
            "question": "Were there other economists who influenced G\u00e9rard Debreu besides Jacques Dr\u00e8ze?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8114640116691589,
            "question": "What is the relationship between G\u00e9rard Debreu and Jacques Dr\u00e8ze?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.761349618434906,
            "question": "Can you name an economist who was influenced by Jacques Dr\u00e8ze?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6399371027946472,
            "question": "What field of study do both G\u00e9rard Debreu and Jacques Dr\u00e8ze likely belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38832759857177734,
            "question": "Who might have been a mentor to G\u00e9rard Debreu?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3336291015148163,
            "question": "What makes G\u00e9rard Debreu's work notable in economics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33137601613998413,
            "question": "How did Jacques Dr\u00e8ze's ideas shape the development of economic theory?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=G\u00e9rard Debreu was influenced by Jacques Dr\u00e8ze.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5869_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What makes G\u00e9rard Debreu's work notable in economics?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5869_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who might have been a mentor to G\u00e9rard Debreu?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5869_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What field of study do both G\u00e9rard Debreu and Jacques Dr\u00e8ze likely belong to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5869_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5869_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5869_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5869_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5869_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5869_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5869_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5869_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5869_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5869_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5869_42.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided documents do not mention Jacques Dr\u00e8ze or any indication that G\u00e9rard Debreu was influenced by him. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the requested format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents do not provide any information about G\u00e9rard Debreu being influenced by Jacques Dr\u00e8ze. The provided context information mainly discusses Debreu's work, awards, and contributions to economics, but does not mention any influences or relationships with other individuals, including Jacques Dr\u00e8ze."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"no\"}\n```\n\nThe provided documents do not mention any influence of G\u00e9rard Debreu by Jacques Dr\u00e8ze. The information focuses on Debreu's contributions to economics, his academic career, and the recognition he received through the Nobel Prize in Economics, but there is no reference to Jacques Dr\u00e8ze or any specific influences on Debreu\u2019s work."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "There is no information provided in the context that suggests G\u00e9rard Debreu was influenced by Jacques Dr\u00e8ze.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "There is no mention of Jacques Dr\u00e8ze or any indication of influence from him in the provided text.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There is no mention of Jacques Dr\u00e8ze influencing G\u00e9rard Debreu in the provided context information.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The provided context does not mention any influence from Jacques Dr\u00e8ze on G\u00e9rard Debreu, nor is there any indication of such an influence in his biographical and professional details.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}